What industry did you ultimately pursue a career in?
So I'm in tech right now. I work for Intel.
Just because I was educated as one,
not because I wanted to be one.
The generation that I come from,
we just told what to do.
We just did it. And later
on in my life I was like,
did I really want to do all
this or did I just do this
just because the society wanted me to do this?
I don't think anybody forced me.
Sometimes you just gotta stop and ask yourself,
what is it that you want to do?
Don't follow the fucking crowd.
You just do you. As simple as that.
You know, in today's world, how can
someone really break into the tech industry?
I think right now, I think the world,
doesn't matter which industry you're in,
you gotta know the right people.
It's got nothing to do with
what you do, how good you are.
If you're a smart person,
you could excel in any field.
Fuckin' tech, attorney, lawyer, whatever. Doesn't matter.
Medical field. As long as you're
a smart guy or smart girl,
you gotta know the right people
and know how to maneuver those conversations.
It's all about people skills.
Doesn't matter which industry you're in.